http://www.iup.edu/privacy/

Skip to main content
Toggle navigation
Indiana University of Pennsylvania
Imagine UnlimitedA–Z IndexFind People
AdmissionsAdmissionsUndergraduate AdmissionsGraduate AdmissionsCook Honors College AdmissionsInternational AdmissionsCulinary AdmissionsSummer SessionsWinter SessionApply NowVirtual Campus VisitsAcademicsAcademicsUndergraduate ProgramsGraduate ProgramsColleges and DepartmentsCook Honors CollegeInterdisciplinary EducationInternships and International EducationOnline LearningOur StudentsOur FacultySpecial ProgramsAcademic SupportIT Support CenterRegistrarCareer and Professional Development CenterIUP LibrariesMyIUPResearchResearchResearch NewsResearch EventsCenters and InstitutesExpertiseResources for ResearchersResearch InstituteUndergraduate Research OfficeStudent ResearchStudent LifeStudent LifeEvents and ActivitiesDining, Housing, and Campus LifeFinancial AidStudent EmploymentCenter for Health and Well-BeingStudent SupportHawks Q&A CenterHawk’s NestParentsStudent Co-opOak GroveCenter for Multicultural Student Leadership and EngagementAlumniAlumniReturning to Campus and the Alumni HouseAlumni AssociationMeet Our AlumniAlumni and Friends NewsAbout IUPAbout IUPIUP at a GlanceCampuses and CentersCommunity ServicesMap, Directions, and ParkingEmployment at IUPAdministrationSupport IUPNews and EventsNews and EventsIUP NewsCentral CalendarIUP MagazineHomecomingFamily WeekendIUP MobileEmergency InformationAcademic Restructuring Plans2020-21 Academic Year Plans and Coronavirus Information
Imagine UnlimitedA–Z IndexFind People
Toggle navigation
Privacy Statement
Contact UsContact Us Form
Attend IUPHelp Students Now
Privacy Statement
Our Use of Cookies
The Indiana University of Pennsylvania (IUP) website uses
Google Analytics to help analyze how users use the site. The Foundation for IUP serves as the registrant for Google products and acts as IUP’s agent for Google products. This analytical tool uses cookies, which are text files placed on your computer, to collect standard Internet log information and visitor behavior information in an anonymous manner. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including your IP address) is transmitted to Google. This information is then used to evaluate visitors’ use of the website and to compile statistical reports on website activity.
IUP will not (and will not allow any third party) to use this statistical analytics tool to collect or track any personally identifiable information about visitors to our site. We will not associate any data gathered from this site with any personally identifying information from any source as part of our use of Google Analytics. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. Neither IUP nor Google will link, or seek to link, an IP address with the identity of a computer user.
Further Information about Cookies
The
About Cookies website, maintained by law firm Pinsent Masons, explains how to delete and control the cookies stored on your computer. Additional information about cookies is available via
Google and
Wikipedia.
Disabling and Enabling Cookies
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies by modifying the settings on your browser. The About Cookies site explains
how to remove cookies from your browser.
Using our Search Engine
Our search engine is powered by Google Custom Search. In order for this search engine to work, search information is passed to Google.
Find People/OnLine Directory Service
Our
online directory service provides only personal information that has been authorized by those listed.
At your request, your address information can be changed, restricted, or removed from the on-line directory. Employees should contact the
Office of Human Resources; students can change their information by
logging into MyIUP.
Online Forms
Information entered into online forms on this website (aside from search forms) may be delivered to its recipients by e-mail. E-mail is not a secure form of communication, and it is possible, though unlikely, that your information could be intercepted and read by a third party while in transit.
If you do not feel comfortable with the possibility of your information being intercepted by a third party, please feel free to contact the appropriate office by mail or by phone. Contact information is provided at the bottom of every page on the site.
Family Education Rights and Privacy Act
IUP is bound by federal law—the Family Education Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA)—to protect the privacy of its students. Any personal information collected by this website is protected by university policy.
Indiana University of Pennsylvania1011 South DriveIndiana, PA 15705
Phone:
724-357-2100
Office HoursMonday through Friday9:00 a.m.–Noon1:00–4:30 p.m.
